When I was in the 4th grade of elementary school, I had a boy's cock.
小学校4年生で男のチンチンを入れた
Yes, hello.
はい、こんにちは
Are you nervous?
緊張します?
I'll do it for a while.
ちょっとしますね
I'm nervous too.
僕も緊張してます
I can't believe I'm in a hotel dressing room like this with such a beautiful person.
こんな綺麗な人とこんなホテルの衣室にいるなんて
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Yes, it's okay.
はい、大丈夫です
How old are you?
お年がいくつだっけ?
I'm 19 years old now.
今19歳です
Isn't it pitchy?
ピッチピチじゃないですか?
No, no.
いや いや
Pitch pichi, right?
ピッチピチでしょ?
19.
19って
I'm starting to feel a little older.
もうちょっとね、年を感じますね
You'll probably think that when you turn 20, right?
それ20歳になった時多分思うんじゃない?
Is that so?
ですかね
But that’s it, right?
でもあれでしょ?
Naturally, the fact that I'm thinking about releasing something like this means that
当然、こういうの出てみようかなと思っているということは、
Are you interested in sex?
エッチには興味がある?
Yes, there is.
ありますね
be?
ある?
yes.
はい
By the way, how old were you when you had your first experience?
ちなみに初体験何歳の時ですか?
My first experience...
初体験が...
Lost barge.
ロストバージ
少女喪失
It's a 4th grade basket.
小4かごですね
picture?
え?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
What did you just say?
今何て言った?
It's a 4th grade basket.
小4かごですね
Small 4?
小4?
It's Japanese, right?
日本語だよね?
It's Japanese.
日本語です
4th grade of elementary school, right?
小学校4年だよね?
that's right.
そうです
It's not Chinese, right?
中国語じゃないよね?
4th grade, right?
小4だよね?
4th grade elementary school?
小学校4年生?
picture?
え?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
When you entered elementary school, you were about 6 years old, the same as me.
君の小学校の入学の時は、やっぱり僕と同じ6歳ぐらいで入学した
Is it?
の かな?
that's right.
そうです
It might fly.
飛び切るかもしれない
If you jump all the way, it will get even worse.
飛び切ったらもっとやばくなるからね
Does that mean she's about 10 years old?
ということは、10歳ぐらいってこと?
I agree.
そうですね
10 years old?
10歳?
10 years old for first experience?
初体験で10歳?
What was your first experience?
何の初体験?
It was my first experience when I was still in the 4th grade of elementary school.
俺、まだ小学校4年生の時って初体験だな
Like going into a high-capacity pool.
高額電容のプールに入るとか
You can go into a pool that is about 1 meter deep.
水 深1メーター30ぐらいのプールに入るとか
That's my first experience though.
そのぐらいが俺の初体験だけど
4th grade.
小 4の
What are you?
君は何?
When I was deciding whether to enter the 130cm pool or not,
僕が130センチのプールに入るか入らないかの時に、
Have you experienced it for the first time yet?
もう初体験したの?
that's right.
そうです
First experience with Edge.
エッジの初体験
Seriously?
マジで?
Well, I'm a little disappointed, but I don't quite agree with that.
え、ちょっと、がぜん、ちょっと納得いかないんですけど
Huh, who is the other person?
え、相手は誰なんですか?
I met my partner through SNS.
相手は、普通にSNSで知り合った
Wait a minute, wait.
ちょっと待って待って
Do 4th graders know about it on SNS?
小学4年生がSNSで知らうの?
I can tell.
知らえますよ
Oh, you didn't think we shouldn't meet?
え、それ、会っちゃいけないとか思わなかった?
Well, at that time, my friend liked cosplay.
なんか、その時は友達がコスプレが好きで
Wait, how old are your friends?
え、友達って何歳?
Elementary school student?
小学生?
Ah, we're the same age.
あ、同じ歳です
Eh, I don't know.
え、ちょっとわかんない
So, I want to meet that cosplay friend,
で、そのコスプレ仲間に会いたいから、
I followed him and was there with him.
ついてきて、みたいな感じで一緒にいたんですよ
How old were the people you met there through SNS?
そこにSNSで知り合ったら、何歳の人がいたの?
At the time, I believe he was in his first or second year of high school.
当時が、確か高1か2って言ってましたね
16, 17 etc.
16、17とか
Seriously?
マジか
10 and 17 years old.
10歳と17歳
Eh, seriously?
え、マジ?
Where is it?
場所はどこ?
Oh, that's what you said?
あ、そういうこと言ってたの?
That's no good.
そこじゃダメよ
The place is like a hotel or your boyfriend's house.
場所ってほら、ホテルとか彼氏の家とか、
That's what it means.
そういう意味ですよ
I was just wondering what they would give me if I was surprised right now.
今びっくりしたら何出すのかと思っただけ
I was shocked.
ドキッとしちゃった
First, I went to a game center and
初 め、ゲームセンターに行って、
From there, we went to karaoke and that was the end of the day.
そこからカラオケ行って、その日はそれと終わりましたね
Where was the first place you rebuilt?
初再建した場所は?
It was the other person's house.
相手の家でした
Ah, home.
あ、家ね
That's scary too.
それも怖いじゃんだって
High school students bring in elementary school students and have sex with them.
高校生が小学生連れ込んでエッチするんだよ
So, I was like, ``Where are you going to do it?''
だ って俺、逆にどこでやるのって、
I thought it couldn't be done anywhere.
どこでもできないと思ったんだよね
It's not like I have a car.
車持ってるわけじゃないじゃん
Do you understand?
分かる?
Even if I brought in myself, I would carry as many elementary school students as round students on my back.
自分自身連れ込んでも、ラウンド生徒背負ってるくらいの小学生を
Isn't that why you're bringing her in?
連 れ込むわけでしょ?
Even though I entered the hotel, I was still a high school student, including myself.
ホテル入ったって、自分も含めてまだ高校生だから、
That's dangerous.
やばいじゃん
At home?
家で?
Did you know you were going to do that?
それやると分かってたの?
But I guess I do something like that.
でも、なんかそういうことするんだな、
Something like that.
みたいなことは
Oh, seriously?
え、マジで?
Did you know?
分かってたの?
I accepted it.
受け入れたんだ
Well, yes.
まあ、はい
The boyfriend I met for the first time was really cool.
その初体験の彼氏がかっこよかったんだ
It was cool.
かっこよかった
Now that I think about it, that's how it is.
今思うとそんななんですけどね
Back then, older men looked cool.
当時は年上の男の人ってかっこよく見えるんで
How was the sex?
エッチどうでした?
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
Yeah, but I remember it being quite difficult to get into.
え、でも、なかなか入りづらかったの覚えてます
It's like sex between a 10 year old and a 17 year old.
なんかね、10歳と17歳のセックスじゃん
If you say it's hard to get into it, the comedians just don't get it.
入りづらいって言われたら、芸員がいまいちピンとこないんだ
Right.
よね
If you were an adult and you were doing this with an adult,
これ がほら大人で、大人の人と君がやってたら、
Oh, I guess her pussy was narrow.
あ、マンコ狭いんだったんだねとか、
I think it's hard to get into it because I'm a girl,
少女だから入りづらいよねと思うけど、
My opponent is 17 so I don't know if I'm good or not.
相手17だから上手いのかどうかも分かんないし、
It's a little difficult to get into,
ちょっとその入りづらいというか、
It's like I can't clearly see the point of failure.
失敗のポイントがよく見えてこないというか
Why was it so hard to get in?
なんで入りづらかったの?
I don't know if I was just not good at it or if my pussy was really small.
ただ下手だったのか、本当にマンコが小さかったのかとか分から
No, right?
ない よね
What do you think about being an artist?
実際、芸員はなんだと思います?
Yeah, but then...
えー、でもそっから...
How many times did you do it?
何 回かやったの?
Do it a few times.
何回かやって
With that person?
その人と?
I thought I could use lotion.
ローションを使えばいいと思って
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
おい、ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って
I'll solve my questions one by one.
一個一個、俺の疑問を解決するよ
Sorry.
ごめんね
Nice idea, just one.
ナイスアイデア、まず一個ね
Nice idea, one, one.
ナイスアイデア、一個、一個
Nice idea!
ナイスアイデア!
Second, who came up with the idea?
次に、そのアイデアは誰から出たの?
I had it.
それは私が持ったんですよ
That's right.
そうだよね
That's what it means.
そういうことだよね
That's what it felt like now.
今そういう感じだったよね
Conversation.
会話がね
You said you thought you could use lotion.
ローションを使えばいいんだと思ったって言ったよね
Well, she's in the fourth grade of elementary school.
えー、小学4年生だよね
Do you wear lotion in fourth grade?
小学4年生でローションをしてるの?
I know.
知ってますよ
why?
なんで?
Since then, I've been wearing it normally and using a rotor.
その時から普通にオネにしてて、ローターを使ってたんだよ、
At that time.
その時は
But I can't get into it by looking it up on the internet.
でもそうやってネットで調べて入んないんだ
That's it, there are so many things to get into, I don't understand anymore.
あれだ、もう突っ込むところが多すぎてもうわかんねえよ、
now.
今
It's completely buggy now.
もう今、完全にバグってるよ
Huh, is there a bug?
え、バグってる?
what?
何?
There's too much information now, so I can't get into it?
今もう情報が多すぎて、おっちゃん入んない?
Which one is it from?
どれからですか?
No, that's all now.
いや、もう全部だよ
What?
え、何?
what happened?
どうしたの?
First time now?
今初めて?
Is this your first time?
オネは初めて?
So thrust.
そう突っ込み
I want to dive into everything.
全てに突っ込みたい
what?
何?
No, no, not anymore.
いやいや、もう
I researched it and thought maybe I could get it in by using lotion.
調べて、ローションを使えば入るんじゃないかと思って
That's what I thought.
思ったんだ
yes.
はい
I don't know what the idea is, but
どういう発想なのかわかんないけど、
Did you succeed there?
そこで成功したの?
Ah, it was successful.
あ、成功しましたよ
Right now, I'm thinking.
今ね、俺はね、思ってる
In a big, vague way, I was glad it wasn't my daughter.
大きくぼんやりと、自分の娘じゃなくてよかったなと
Hahaha, follow me.
あ ははは、たがってね
If it were my daughter, I'd be pretty shocked right now.
自分の娘だったら、今もうかなりショックだよね
After hearing this story, I feel like I'm already drinking sake today.
今日はもう焼け酒だね、この話聞いたらね
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうなんだ
That's smart.
賢いね
yes.
はい
Well, you've solved everything.
ね、よく何も解決したね
At that H.
そのエイチで
My parents don't think so.
と思わない、親は
Well, that's really what it means.
ね、ほんとそういうことですよ
Seriously?
まじか
Elite, elite.
エリートだね、エリート
elite.
エリート
You did your best, Elite.
頑張りました、エリートです
The army's solution skills are like that of a general.
軍隊の解決技は将軍さんみたいなね
It's about the same difference between a general and a two-headed soldier.
将軍と二頭兵くらいの違いですけどね
It's elite.
エリートですよ
Well, that's a bit like that.
ね、ちょっとあれですね
I'm also feeling the generation cap in many ways right now.
僕も今、いろんなね、ジェネレーションキャップを感じてますよ
I made her a woman.
女にしてた
I made it a woman.
女にしてました
with rotor.
ローターで
It's a rotor.
ローターです
In elementary school.
小学生で
The rotor of an elementary school student and a woman with a rotor,
小学生でローターで女にのそのローターは、
what?
何?
Maybe I'll ask Santa or something to give me shoes as a Christmas present.
もしかしてサンタさんとかにお願いしてクリスマスプレゼントで靴
Did it go under there or something?
下 に入ってたりとかしたの?
No, then, um.
いや、そしたらね、あのー
If that's the case, then I'll give up too.
もうそれだったらそうで俺も諦めるからね
I'm not saying that it's like a family or something like that.
そういう何か家庭なのかなとかも言ってないけど
I usually buy it online without telling them.
普通に内緒で通販で買って
Well, you don't have to tell me anything, you'll know.
もうね、内緒付けなくても分かるから
No, no.
いや いや
If you buy it online, you can't tell me anything about it.
通販で買うっていうか、君の場に内緒しかないからね
That's right.
そうなんだ
Just buy it on Amazon.
アマゾンで買っちゃえばよ
If you buy it on Amazon, it has a rotor in it.
アマゾンで買ったらローターって入ってるからね
It was in, it was in.
入ってました、入ってました
So just buy it from that shady specialty site.
だからちょっとあの、いかがわしい専門のサイトで買ってみ
I did.
ました
Something bad happened.
悪 事はあったんだね
Ah, there it was.
あ、ありましたね
Eh, I've been using a rotor since my 4th grade at super high school.
え、超学校4年生からローター使ってたら、
The vibrations of the waves won't even sway you, right?
波の振動じゃもうじくともしないでしょ?
Yes, you get used to it, after all.
そう、なんか慣れますね、やっぱり
You'll definitely get used to it, right?
絶対慣れるでしょ?
It's no longer possible to use rotors.
ローターじゃ今はもう無理ですね
Rotor, rotor, it's no longer possible.
ローター、ローターじゃ、今じゃもう無理
Did you hear that, everyone?
聞きましたか、皆さん
Humans have no choice but to provide food for evolution.
人間が進化の糧でさせるしかないんですよね
That's what evolution is all about.
そういうもんで進化っていうのはね
I see.
なるほど
19 years old.
19歳
I'm 19 years old.
19歳です
19 years old.
19歳
No more rotors.
ローターじゃもうダメ
That's cool.
かっこいいね
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
I'm a nice person, but if I haven't used a rotor before, I'll say it's hot.
俺、いい人だけど、今までにローター使ってないとヒーって言
It's going to happen.
っちゃ うからね
Please stop heating.
ヒーやめてください
That's what we say.
って 言っちゃうからね、俺らの
That's right.
そうなんだ
After that, it was a defeat.
後に敗戦ですね
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
By the way, since I was in the 4th grade of elementary school,
ちなみにじゃあ、そんな小学校4年生からってことは、
If it's raw liver, it's eaten, right?
生肝体だと食い取りですでしょ?
It's all about eating.
食い取りですよね
Right?
でしょ?
I was really surprised when I told them it was actually chikumi.
ここね、実はチクミですとか言ってたらめっちゃびっくりしたんだ
hey.
ね
Chikumi?
チ クミかよって
People these days definitely eat raw liver, right?
絶対食い取り、今の人だともう絶対生肝で食い取りですよね、
someday.
いつか
That's right.
そうですよね
hey.
ね
Good, that's correct.
よかった、正解だよね
So it's better to take advantage of others than to be friends with them.
じゃあ仲よりも食い取りするのがいいんだ
I like to eat food.
食い取り好きですね
yes.
はい
So, even though you're 19 now, do you have a boyfriend?
じゃあ、今19でも、彼氏いるの?
Are you not there?
いないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
Well then, I like it for women.
じゃあ、女には好きなんだ
I like it.
好きです
Even now.
今でも
yes.
はい
I see, how many times a week do you do this to women?
そっか、女に週何回ぐらいやってるの?
But lately, I've been in that situation, and if I do it every day, I get used to it.
でも、最近はその中だ、毎日やると慣れるってのもあって、
I guess I'll do it once a week.
週1とかやるとね
I still don't know why I suddenly applied the brakes when I came here.
ここに来て急にブレーキがかかった理由が今じゃわかんないけど
hey.
ね
Why are the brakes suddenly applied like this?
な ぜ急にこうブレーキがかかってるの?
hey.
ね
Please consider these tips when taking the exam.
受験の時に考えてください、そのヒントに
Like when I was 17 or when I went to high school.
17とか高校行く時とかね
No, I don't think there's any need to pick up the phone anymore.
いや、なんか電話の上ってもうないじゃないですか
On the phone?
電話の上?
That's what I thought about.
そこを考えちゃったんだ
Yes, I thought that if I could use the phone, there would be no next time.
そう、もし電話になれたらもう次がないと思って
Yeah.
うん
I thought about what's on the phone.
電話の上は何かっていうことを考えたんだ
yes.
そう
That's amazing.
すーごいね
I've never thought about that either.
俺もそんなこと考えたことないよ
I wonder what's next after the phone call.
電話の次は何かなとか
I've already added the wheel rotation completely.
もう 完全に輪回転を足しちゃったことだ
Isn't that what you mean?
ってことでしょ?
Jump over the wall, jump over the wall of humanity's heroes,
もう壁をね、人類の英雄を飛び越えて壁をね、
So you decided what to do when you broke it?
ぶち破った時どうしたらいいのってことになったわけでしょ?
That's cool.
かっこいいね
No, no.
いやいや
I think I should leave now.
もういっちゃえばいいと思う
To the limit.
限界まで
Ahhh.
ああー
If I can't make phone calls anymore, I'll be at the construction site.
電話とかもう無理だったら工事現場のドドドドドドドドドドドドド
Do Do.
ド ド
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
ド ドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドドド
Do do do do do do do do.
ド ドドドドドドドド
Well, I guess that doesn't make sense.
あるのとさ、これではどうだみたいな
As expected.
さすがにね
Women are amazing, aren't they?
女人ってすごいよね
I put it in an apartment or something.
マンションとかに入れたよ
Please take a little break.
もう少し休憩してください
No, it's embarrassing.
いや、 恥ずかしいですよ
I don't think it's the same.
まさか同じと思ってないよ
It's only about 2.7 on Sundays though.
日曜だいぶ2.7くらいしかないですけど
Isn't it okay to go that far?
そこまで行っちゃえばいいじゃないですか
I feel like going there though.
行ってみたい気持ちがしますけどね
Do you feel like going there?
行ってみたい気持ちがする?
yes.
はい
Eh, scary.
えー、怖い
M's writing depends on the partner, right?
Mの書って、パートナーによるじゃないですか
in the end.
結局
I don't feel like there's a partner that somehow surpasses you.
何となくあなたを超えるパートナーがいるような気がしない
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
It's like there's a person a head above you wearing a dress that looks like it's coming.
君よりも頭一つ上にこう、 来てるようなドレスの人がいるような
I don't feel like it.
気 がしないし
If so, I really don't know what would happen.
もしいたとしたら、本当にどうなるかわからないよね
surely.
確かに
I don't know if I will come back alive.
生きて帰ってこないかわからない
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Thank you for your help, Pritoris.
お世話になったらプリトリス
Don't you like boobs that much?
あんまりウッパイ好きじゃないの?
I also like uppai.
ウッパイも好きです
How many cups of this?
何カップのこれ?
It's C.
Cです
OK
like.
好 き
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
What do you like about your body?
自分の体のどこが好き?
Tell me everything, including your face.
顔とかも全部言えて
Is it your favorite place?
好きなところですか?
Do you have a surprising complex?
意外とコンプレックスあるの?
No, everything.
いや、全部だよ
If you say you have a complex,
君がコンプレックスって言うのだったら、
It's all about the other guys.
ほかの奴にみんな打ち込みだよ
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
It's going to be really sudden.
もう本当に唐突されちゃう
I don't have a favorite place.
好きなところないです
Is that so?
そうなの?
Even though it's so beautiful.
こんな美しいのに
I hate it all.
全部嫌だ
I quite like it myself.
結構自分の好きだよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Is that so?
そうなの?
A place where people can praise you.
人に褒められる場所
Upper body.
上半身
It only monitors the upper body.
上半身しか監視しないからね
If it's a big deal, considering the time spent on this question,
どえらいわけだったら、 この質問の時間の割には、
That's a painful answer.
痛いな答えが
Is it above?
上ですか?
What do you like about America?
アメリカのどこが好き?
Is it North America?
北アメリカかな?
There's no question like that.
そんな質問ないでしょ
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I get praised.
褒 められるんだ
Well, that's it.
じゃあ、あれだ
It's slippery.
すべしてる
I'm the only one who knows right now.
俺しか今分かってないんだけど
By the way, what do your nipples look like?
ちなみに乳首が、 なーに見えたーっているよ
My nipples are sore.
乳首がたーっているよ
why?
なんで?
My nipples are sore.
乳首がたーっているよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Touched by this old man?
こんなおっさんに触られて?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sorry.
ごめんね
I have nothing but gratitude.
感謝 しかないからね
Feeling grateful.
感謝の気持ちを
Oh, it wasn't Mike.
あ、マイクじゃなかった
Ah, this.
あ、これ
Isn't this a phone?
電話じゃないですか、これ
It's a phone call.
電話ですよ
I didn't notice it now.
気がつかなかったわ、今
It feels better to be closer.
近くの方が気持ちいいんだ
yes.
はい
I don't know where to attack, but it's M.
どこが攻めていいのか、 でもMなんだ
M Don't do it.
Mいけません
Can you do both?
両方いける?
I want to bully you.
いじめたいです
That's right.
そう なんだ
Thank you, thank you.
ありがとう、ありがとう
I'm angry because life is tight.
生活タイトだから、俺怒って
Life is tight.
生活タイトです
First, let me take this off.
まず、これ脱いちゃおうか
Should I take it off?
脱いちゃうか
take off
脱い
Chau.
ちゃ う
What is this small areola?
なにこの小さな乳輪は
Why are these small areolas?
なんでこの小さな乳輪は
You're pretty proud of this.
これ結構自慢でしょ
No, isn't that normal?
いや、そんな普通じゃないですか
It's better to say, but if you don't play, you'll think you're not playing.
言った方がいいけど、遊んでないには 遊んでないって思われる特
Especially the nipples, aren't they?
殊 乳首じゃないですか
No, it's not.
いや、違う
I'm not playing.
遊んでないですよ
Really?
本当に?
How many men have experience?
男性経験は何人?
Really?
本当に?
That's right.
そうなんだ
I'm 10 years old and write well.
10歳よく書くね
9 years.
9年
Is that so?
そう か
I'm not playing.
遊んでないんだ
遊んでないですよ
why?
なんで?
If you tell me you're 10 years old, I'm sure you'll think I'm playing around.
10歳ですって言われたら 遊んでると思われてもおかしくない
Yes, it is.
です よ
No, no, no.
いや、いや、いや
So how many men have you dated seriously?
じゃあ、真剣に付き合った男性何人?
Seriously?
真剣に?
Moreover.
しかも
That's right.
そうなんだ
Let's talk about that first.
そこに話最初にしておこうよ
That's why it's going to go up.
こうなると上がるんだからさ
No, no, no.
いや、いや、いや
That's it.
そんな
You don't have a boyfriend, right?
ついも彼氏ないでしょ
do not have.
ない
Who is your ideal man?
理想の男性どう人?
Ideal man?
理想の男性?
It's okay to be rich.
お金持ちながってもいいんだよ
Right?
で しょ?
I'll accompany you.
俺が付き合うよ
Don't introduce me.
紹介しないで
I'll accompany you.
俺が付き合うよ
I’m being held.
俺が抱かれる
Yeah.
うん
By the way, what are you thinking about when you're talking to a woman?
ちなみに女にしてるときは 何で考えてるの?
I'm watching it.
見てますね
Manga.
マンガ
Erotic manga.
エロいマンガ
It's like Doraemon.
ドラえもんとちゃうよね
It's not.
じゃないですよ
It's like an erotic manga.
エロいマンガみたいな
What is that erotic manga series?
そのエロいマンガのシリーズは何?
Like being raped.
レイブされてたりとかさ
There are various things.
なんかいろいろあるんですけど
There is only massage type.
マッサージ系しかない
Massage type?
マッサージ系?
It's done.
出来上がってるよ
I can't go back.
戻れないよ
I'm 19 years old and I'm getting more and more comfortable with erotic manga and massage.
19歳でエロマンガ マッサージ系って どんどん気持ちよくな
Isn't that what you're saying?
って くるでしょ?
Isn't that what happens when you notice?
気がついたらってやつでしょ?
In that manga, when a strange drug was put on my hand and I did this...
変な薬を手にかけられて こうやってやったら あのマンガで
Sho?
しょ?
That's definitely strange.
絶 対おかしいよ
That's definitely weird.
絶対おかしいよ
Well, really, it's not an entrance.
もうね、本当にね 入り口じゃないからね
It's closer to the exit either way.
どっちかと出口に近いからね
Too bad though.
悪いけど
Erotic manga featuring men who look like normal cool guys
普通のカッコいいやつのような 男の人が出るようなエロマンガ
If you do just one thing at a time, you'll be able to become a cool guy.
とか ちょっとひとつひとつなら カッコいい男の人に ときめ
A common erotic manga where you are the first to get fucked.
いて 最初にやられちゃうとか そういうよくある エロマンガ
Because I looked too close to the exit.
から 見すぎて 出口に近いからね
There are so many different meanings in English, like a man's squirting.
英語にもういろんな感じすぎて 男の潮吹きとかね
I'm saying it's close to something like that.
なんかそういうのに近いとか言ってるよ
Really.
本当に
That's what I saw.
そういうの見てんだ
Because if you go for a normal massage, it's a normal massage.
だってそれでさ 普通のマッサージとか行ったら 普通のマッサ
I'm getting a little wet though.
ージ なのに もうちょっと濡れちゃうじゃん
I've never had a massage before.
私マッサージ行ったことないんですよね
Not yet.
まだまだ
Really.
本当に
Even a normal massage will make you wet.
普通のマッサージも濡れちゃうよ
Okay, massage type.
いいですよ、マッサージ系
Is that what you're doing?
それでこうすんだ?
What should I do?
どうしよう
Really?
本当に?
That's cool.
かっこいいね
It's cool.
かっこいいよ
It's really cool.
本当かっこいいよ
That's right.
そうなんだ
I can't give you a massage, but that's how it is, right?
マッサージはできないけど こういうことでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
Rub and twirl.
こすりくるくる
gradually.
だんだん
It'll leave your body alone.
体をほってくるよね
that's right.
そうです
If you feel like it.
気がついたらね
You just exceeded it.
さっき超えちゃってましたね
Why would you exceed it?
なんで超えちゃうんだろうね
That's strange, isn't it?
おかしいよね
Really?
本当に?
I have to talk to my parents today.
今日、両親と話しなきゃいけない
Look at your parents.
両親を見なさい
Yesterday, I told my parents something important.
昨日、両親に重大なことを伝えました
Really.
本当に
Mom and dad, nice to meet you.
お父さん、お母さん、初めまして
This is my husband.
主人です
I have a very important announcement today.
今日はとても重要なお知らせがあります
My daughter is Fujinoyama.
娘さんは藤の山です
It's a hidden egg.
隠卵な です
Your daughter has congenital cryptogenic syndrome.
あなたの娘さんは 先天性の隠卵症候群です
No.
なかりません
In modern medicine.
現代の医学では
Mom and dad, finally.
お父さん、お母さん、ようやく
That's true.
本当そうですよ
What should I do?
どうするの?
Is it genetic?
遺伝ですか?
If you say it.
言 ったら
Unexpected genetics.
まさかの遺伝
The beginning of genetics.
まさかの遺伝初め
Open it again.
じゃんも開けなおって
That's right.
そうだよね
It feels good here.
ここが気持ちいいんだ
It'll get dirty.
汚れちゃう
Let's have it removed.
抜いてもらいましょう
The cat gets dirty.
猫が汚れちゃう
Why?
なんでやねん
Wipe the tide.
潮拭いたり
Wouldn't it be bad if you did that?
あれしちゃうとまずいじゃないですか
Let's have it removed.
抜いてもらいましょう
I don't feel naughty.
やらしい気持ちないですよね
It's true.
本当です
clean.
クリーン
It's treatment now.
今は治療ですから
Because it feels naughty.
やらしい気持ちなので
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
It's a world of treatment.
治療の世界ですよ
Because I heard what you just said.
今の話を聞いたわけだから
This isn't erotic.
これはエロじゃないよ
It's Nasural Diographic.
ナシュラルディオグラフィックですよ
It's close to the wild kingdom.
野生の王国に近いですよ
It feels good here.
ここが気持ちいいんだ
This is a weakness, but it's no good.
このくらいは弱みだけど、 ダメなんだ
It will make you feel better and stronger.
ちょっと気持ちよくなって 強くしますね
It's a mess for the first time.
初めちゃくちゃだね
It's like how to cook delicious rice.
おいしいご飯の炊き方みたいだよね
That's interesting.
面白いよね
A lot of my bad things come out.
俺の悪いところがいっぱい出ちゃう
It won't be naughty.
やらしくならないじゃん
I think it will change the way I take money from myself when I answer the phone.
電話を当てるときに 自分から食いとりするのが 変わると思い
Chau?
ちゃ う?
I usually call from above my pants.
普段はパンツの上から 電話するんですよ
why?
なんで?
There's something different about a chock.
チョックだと なんか違うんですよ
I don't think it's a comfortable place to hit it, but rather, it's through my pants.
気 持ちよく当てる位置っていうか 違って パンツ越しが ちょ
It's so good, isn't it?
う どいいんですよね
I'm a little particular about it.
ちょっとこだわりがあるんだ
I don't know.
わかんねぇ
I really don't understand.
超わかんねぇ
I don't know, but it's kind of cool.
わかんないけど なんかかっこいいね
I don't like having that kind of commitment.
そういうこだわりを持ってるって 好きじゃないけど
But I don't know.
でもわかんない
It's a good time right now, so guess these pants.
今ちょうどいいから このパンツを当ててくれ
That's fine.
いいですよ
I'll try making it a little stronger.
ちょっと強くしてみるね
Ah, I just arrived.
あ、ちょっと着きました
I have arrived.
着きました
I don't know if that's real beef.
それ が本当の牛肉は わかんない
It's finally okay.
いよいよ大丈夫ですよ
To my father, from my father, I don't even know how old I am.
お父さんに お父さんより 僕の年齢もわかんない
Ahahahaha
あはははは
The way they react is so realistic.
反 応の仕方がリアルよ
to max
マックスに
The sound was getting louder and louder.
音 が 上っ気に当たらしていった
From the other side of my pants.
パンツの向こうから
Please do it.
やらしてね
What are you doing?
何してる?
Look.
見て
I'm supposed to hit you.
叩くなってるよ
I'm polypoly.
ポ リポリしてる
You can tell by pressing your pants.
パンツを押しても分かるね
I'm polypoly.
ポリポリしてる
I think I can go.
行けそう
You can go.
行っていいよ
go.
行く
That's suspicious.
怪しいね
Mr. Panties is getting stronger and faster.
パンツさんが もう一足早く 強くなってるよ
It's not cloudy.
濁ってないね
This part is amazing, Nail.
この あそこが すごいね、ネイル
I don't care though.
どうでもいいけど
The nails are included and the whole picture is well...
ネイルが入って 全体像が まあ、
But this is a 4th grade elementary school student who was watching a man's penis.
でもこれが 小学校4年生で 男のチンチンを
Isn't that good?
いい じゃないですか
Hey, it's forbidden
ちょっと ね、禁断の
What do you do?
何 するんですか?
This sound.
この音が
There's a sound.
音がするよ
Noisy.
ノイジーな
What is this?
これ何ですか?
That's it.
あれですよ
It felt good just now.
さっき気持ちよかったんでね
This clitty feeling.
この クリティな感じがね
Isn't it nice?
いいじゃないですか
A spring that comes out.
出る泉
But I'm more of a clear person than a medium person.
でも中よりもクリア派なんだ
If anything, I like both.
どっちかって言えば 両方好きだけど
This is heavy.
これ重めね
It's small again.
また小さいね
This little heavy thing from earlier
こんな この小さな重めが さっきの
Was it painful?
痛 かった?
It tickled.
くすぐった
Did it tickle?
くすぐった?
After going.
行った後
After I go.
行った後ね
That's a bit like that.
ちょっとあれだね
Is it better not to have a country?
国とかしないほうがいい?
You love the country, right?
国好きでしょ
I think the country is probably okay.
国は多分大丈夫と思う
I either love the country or hate it.
国好きか嫌いだけど
You love the country, right?
国好きでしょ
You've always loved the country, haven't you?
ずっと国好きでしょ
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
Can I lick it?
舐めちゃっていい?
This pussy.
この まんこ
tickles.
くすぐったい
What should I do?
どうしたらいいの?
Be kind.
やさしめに
Hold your feet.
足持って
It's finished.
出来上がってるんだよ
By the way, that's good.
ちなみに いいんだね
copper?
どう?
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
く すぐったい?
This tickles.
これくすぐったいですね
You'll feel better right away.
すぐ気持ちよくなるよ
Can you become one?
なれますか?
Use your phone to clean the cleat chamber, stain only this area, and the entire bottom.
電話でクリート室を ここだけを汚して ここだけを 全体を 底
Raise it up and say something like this
上 げして こう いう 感じで
It's springing up.
湧 きちゃって
That's true.
ほんとそうだね
If the bones become thinner, you'll feel better.
骨があるところは 薄くなっていったら 気持ちよくなる
It's ticklish, isn't it?
くすぐったいでしょ?
This will make everything feel better.
これ ね、全部気持ちよくなるからね
I'm fidgety.
そわそわってする
Right?
そう でしょ?
When it starts to feel good, when my boyfriend and I are wearing normal clothes, I touch him like this and it feels good.
気持ちよくなると 彼氏と普通に服着てて こうやって触って気持
It gets better, so when I'm really waiting for a movie or something.
ち よくなるから 本当に映画とか なんか待ってる時とか
This is so convenient.
すごい 便利なんだよ、これ
It's okay to wear clothes.
服着ててもいいね
Holding hands like this
手繋いでこうやって
It's because it's a pervert that it's done.
変 態だから出来上がってくるの
By the way, when did you add a penis?
ちなみに、おちんちん加えたのいつ?
Did you add a dick?
ちんちん加えたの?
The 4th generation...
その4世...
At the time of Showa 4?
昭和4の時?
Time was a little licking.
時はちょっと舐めた
That's when I licked it.
舐めた時だね
I licked it a little.
ちょっと舐めた
So there's an anniversary to celebrate the day you seriously licked it?
本格的に舐めたっていう 記念日があるわけ?
Anniversary, I made my full-scale debut as a fedostrich.
アニバーサリーな 本格的にフェダチョウデビューしました
Is there a day like that?
っていう 日があるの?
It's really like Chiru Chiro.
本当になんか チルチロみたいな
When will a proper feda debut?
ちゃんとしたフェダのフェダデビューをいつ?
You debuted at Feda in 1st place.
フェダデビューは1位ですね
Are you in between?
あいだ入ってんの?
I came in.
入ってきました
It was so open that I don't know why it was opened there.
なんでそこに開いたのか分かんないぐらい開いたね
It started early though.
スタート早かったのにね
That's a little normal.
そこちょっと普通だね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you good at fedostriches?
フェダチョウ得意?
Do you like fedostasis?
フェダチョウすんの好き?
I love Fedostrich.
俺フェダチョウさん大好き
That's not true.
違うね
You hated me.
俺が嫌いだったのね
Actually a little bit.
ちょっと実は
On the contrary, you should tell me why you asked such a question.
むしろ逆に なんでそんな質問したんだって話しなきゃ
Great, I love Fedostrich too.
よかった、俺もフェダチョウさん大好き
hey.
ね
That's what this is all about.
とことが、この中ではあれだね
That too.
あれもだね
It's a fedostrich.
フェダチョウだね
Fedostrich please.
フェダチョウお願いします
First of all, be gentle.
まずは優しく
Hand, nice.
ハンド、いいな
Hands, hands.
手、手で
Because your fingers are clean.
指きれいだからね
copper
どう
Do you like fedostriches?
いう フェダチョウが好きなの?
For example, I like to add a crying scene and then make it hard.
例えば、泣いてるところから加えて 固くするのが好きとか
However, I like to add something crunchy.
でもやっぱ、私は カチカチのを加えるのが好きです
Ah, it's not quite as clicky right now.
あ、今ちょっとカチカチじゃないね
Tick-tock.
カチカチ
For me, I don't really get ticked off.
俺ね、カチカチってあんまりなことないですからね
Yes, it's okay.
はい、大丈夫です
Is this okay?
ちょっといいですか?
Very.
とっても
Ah, I see.
あ、 なるほどね
You want to do it on time.
時間にちゃんとやりたいはずね
Jiji Son is the one who is missing.
ジラジソンいなくない人ね
I understand.
わかりますよ
I'm sorry, really.
すいません、本当に
Somatsu is gone.
ソ マツはもう
I'm sure you're going to throw it away right away.
すぐビンビンに捨てようとするはずね
I know, I know.
わかるわかる
I understand.
わかりますよ
There is.
いるんですよ
People who enter from Kantama.
金玉から入る人とか
What kind of people are there?
どんな人がいるんですけど
Nowadays, you're the kind of person who wants to make things work as quickly as possible.
今ではもう、早くカチカチにさせようという 人ですよね
It's totally fine.
全然大丈夫ですよ
This will be praised, right?
これ褒められるでしょ?
You'll be praised, right?
褒められるでしょ?
You, etc.
お前ね、とか
Is there anyone who would say this?
これ言っちゃう人いるでしょ?
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
Ah, I quickly became a person who was admired.
あ、あっという間に 褒 め ら れる 人になっちゃった
That's strange.
おかしいな
あれ おかしいな
why?
なんで?
Did you see or do any research?
何か見て研究したの?
I remembered it naturally.
自然と覚えましたね
Did you remember it naturally?
自 然と覚えたの?
It's a great environment.
すごい環境だね
I remember it naturally.
自然と覚えるんだ
Are you really saying this?
これ本当に言っちゃうでしょ?
I love dick.
おちんちん大好きなんだ
yes.
はい
I especially like seeing a penis for the first time.
特に初めて見るおちんちんがいいんだ
The first thing.
初物が
I'm kind of interested.
なんか 興味がね
It seems very interesting.
興味津々な感じです
What do you think of this, penis?
これどうですか、おちんちんは?
That's pretty good, though.
なかなかですね、でも
Quite?
なかなか?
Karakura's evaluation.
からくつの評価が
But it feels good.
でもいい感じですよ
The balls look nice.
玉がいい感じでね
Do your balls feel good?
玉がいい感じ?
A ball?
玉か
I wanted to be praised.
蚤褒められたかった
The balls don't really matter.
玉はあんまり関係ないもんね
The hardness is just right.
硬さはちょうどいいぐらいです
Not really messed up or stiff,
めちゃめちゃ、 ガチガチでもなく、
It's not too tight either.
あ んまりギュリギュリでもなく
Isn't it Funchajin?
ふんちゃじんじゃない?
yes.
そう
The hardness and size of my penis are good,
おちんちんの硬さとか大きさがよくて、
Will you fall in love with me?
好きになったりするの?
Is there such a thing?
そういうことあるの?
Just your penis?
おちんちんだけ?
Well, that's not true, but even if you're a really nice person,
う ーん、 それはないけど、 すごいいい人でも、
If your penis is very delicate,
おちんちんがすごい微妙だったら、
You may end up not liking it.
好きじゃなくなることがあります
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's tough.
厳しいね
You won't tell me that, right?
それ伝えないでしょ?
You can't tell me that, right?
それは伝えないでしょ?
I don't think that's true, since he doesn't say that.
それは、さすがに言わないから、 ちょっとうんって思いますね
I'm particular about it.
こだわりがあるね
こだわりが
Let's see if it's the penis you're looking for.
こだわりのおちんちんかどうかを 確かめてみようよ
yes.
そう
good?
いい?
Why don't you just lie there for a while?
ちょっとそこに寝てごらん?
First, how about opening your legs?
まず、 足開けば?
Hey, let's put this in.
ちょっとこれさ、 入れてみましょう
Let's put it in.
入 れてみましょう
penis.
おちんちん
Try putting it in.
入れてみて
Live?
生で?
born.
生
why?
なんで?
Everything is delicious raw.
なんでも生がおいしいじゃん
surely.
確かに
Is there anything delicious that isn't raw?
生じゃなくておいしいことある?
Not really.
ないね
Right?
そう でしょ?
Which is better: beer or draft beer?
ビールと生ビールはどっちがいい?
It's draft beer.
生ビールですね
Raw is better.
生のがいいじゃん
That's all I can think of though.
それぐらいしか思いつかないけど
This is still a test.
これでも検査だからね
Enter it only once.
一回だけ入れましょう
Not told?
言われない?
It's small.
狭いよ
narrow.
狭い
I can only put in about half of it.
半分くらいしか入れない
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's not my opinion.
俺の感想じゃないんだ
Where is it?
どこなの?
It's really good.
めっちゃいい
Is it really good?
めっちゃいい?
Go again.
もう一回行って
It's really good.
めっちゃいい
I received it.
いただきました
It's very narrow.
すごい狭い
It's okay to live, right?
生大丈夫でしょ?
A lot came out.
いっぱい出た
A lot more came out than yesterday.
昨日よりいっぱい出たよね
More came out than yesterday.
昨日よりいっぱい出た
It's different when you have a good woman.
女がいいと違うんだな
I did it yesterday.
昨日やったんですけど
As for sex.
セ ックスは
There are quite a lot of them today.
今日のも全然いっぱい出てますよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
That the girl is beautiful.
女の子がきれいだと
Something cheerful.
元気いいなもので
My knowledge of people too.
僕の人知もね
That's how I react.
そうするのに反応しちゃうんですよ
If I get pregnant.
もし妊娠したら
I'll give it a name.
僕 が名前つけますから
I'm not saying I know people.
人知すると言ってませんけどね
Just the name.
名前だけね
I'll give it a name.
名前はつけますから
yes.
はい
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
With a V sign.
Vサインで
Big success.
大成功
cute.
かわいい